A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 1998-2014 (bulk 2010-2013)
Library of Virginia
- Series III: Subject files, 1998-2013., Extent: 6.65 cu. ft. (19 boxes) (Box 20-38)
  - US Chamber of Commerce, Virginia Roundtable, 2010 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Asian Advisory Board, 2003-2008 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Beach Arena, 2012 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Biotechnology Research Partnership Authority, 2010 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Biotechnology Research Partnership Authority, 2010-2011 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Biotechnology Research Partnership Authority, Board of Directors, 2010 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Biotechnology Research Partnership Authority, Meetings, 2011 October 18 (Box 33, Folder 2-3)
  - Virginia Biotechnology Research Partnership Authority, Meetings, 2011 December 6 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Biotechnology Research Partnership Authority, Meetings, 2012 December 4 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Biotechnology Research Partnership Authority, Meetings, 2013 February 5 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Biotechnology Research Partnership Authority, Meetings, 2013 April 30 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Biotechnology Research Partnership Authority, Meetings, 2013 April 30 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Dept. of Business Assistance, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Chamber of Commerce, 2013 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Commercial Space Flight Authority, 2010 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Commission on Military and National Security Facilities, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Community Capacity Building Initiative, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Early Childhood Foundation, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Economic Development Partnership, 2010-2011 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Economic Development Partnership, 2012-2013 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, 2009-2010 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Futures Forum, 2011 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Golf Trail, 2011 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Homebuilders Association, 2011 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Innovation Partnership, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Virginia-Israel Advisory Board, 2010-2013 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Modeling and Simulation Advisory Council, 2009 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Virginia National Defense Industrial Authority, 2011 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Prisoner and Juvenile Offender Reentry Council, 2010 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Resources Authority, Recovery zone bonds, 2010 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Resources Authority, Report, 2010 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Resources Authority, Board packet, 2010 June (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Resources Authority, Meetings, 2010 June (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Resources Authority, Briefings, 2010 June-August (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Resources Authority, Meetings, 2010 September (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Resources Authority, Meetings, 2010 December (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Resources Authority, Meetings, 2011 March (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Resources Authority, Meetings, 2011 June (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Resources Authority, Meetings, 2011 August (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Resources Authority, Meetings, 2011 September (Box 36, Folder 6-7)
  - Virginia Resources Authority, Meetings, 2011 October (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Resources Authority, Meetings, 2011 December (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Resources Authority, Meetings, 2012 September (Box 37, Folder 2-3)
  - Virginia Resources Authority, Meetings, 2013 March (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Retail Federation, 2010 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Small Business Financing Act, 2010 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Tobacco Indemnification and Community Revitalization Commission, 2010 (Box 37, Folder 7-8)
  - Virginia Tobacco Commission, Meetings, 2011 September (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Tobacco Commission, Meetings, 2012 January (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Tobacco Commission, Meetings, 2012 May (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Tobacco Commission, Meetings, 2012 September (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Tobacco Commission, Meetings, 2013 January (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Tourism Corporation, 2010 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Virginia University Research Partnership, Inc., 2009 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Virginia University Research Partnership, Inc., 2011 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Virginia University Research Partnership, Inc., 2012 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Voluntary Protection Program, 2011 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Workforce Council, 2010-2011 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Virginia for Reliable Energy, ca. 2010 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Washington Commanders Training Camp, 2012 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - The Year of the Entrepreneur, 2012 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Series IV: Development Projects and Initiatives, 2009-2013., Extent: 1.05 cu. ft. (3 boxes) (Box 39-41)
  Series IV: Development Projects and Initiatives is housed in three boxes and is arranged alphabetically by folder title. This series documents the projects and initiatives of the Secretary's office relating to development.
  - Agriculture and Forest Economic Development Workshop, 2011 November 22 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Alternative Fuel Vehicle Plan Development Strategy, undated (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - APEX Wind Energy, undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - CIT Energy Fund, 2010 October 12 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Dominion Wind Power Project, 2010 July 30 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Dominion Virginia Power-Generation Expansion Plan, 2010-2011 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Dept. of Mines, Minerals, and Energy- Guidance Surface Mining Strategy, 2011 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Energy Plan, General Assembly Session, 2010-2011 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Energy Advisory Workshop, 2011 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Energy, 2010 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Energy Plan, 2010 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Fibrowatt, 2011 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Governor McDonnell's Energy Agenda, 2010-2013 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Governor's Energy Summit, 2010 October 17 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Governor McDonnell's Northern California Marketing Trip, 2010 November 14-16 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Governor McDonnell's Marketing mission to Netherlands, UK, and Germany, 2010 July 17-24 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Governor McDonnell's New York City Marketing mission, 2011 May 3 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Governor McDonnell's Mission to Japan, China and South Korea, 2011 May 6-17 (Box 40, Folder 2-3)
  - Guide for Planning and Executing Governor's Investment and Trade Mission, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - James C. Justice Companies, 2011 December 2 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Life Sciences Initiative, 2011 December (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - MARC Green Jobs Consortium, 2010 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Mitsubishi Nuclear Energy Systems, 2011 June 28 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Norfolk Southern, Freight Car America, 2011 February 21 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Offshore Drilling Safety Update, 2011 September 31 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - OSWA Conference, 2010 October 5 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Sec. Cheng Japan visit, 2010 June 27-July 1 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Small Business Workshop, 2011 October 3 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - SWVA Trip, 2011 May (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Tax, 2011 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - TECRO/Taiwan, 2009-2010 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Energy Plan, 2010 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - VOWDA (Virginia Offshore Wind Development Authority), 2010 December 7 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - VOWDA, 2011 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - VOWDA, 2011 March 31 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - VOWDA, 2011 June 14 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Worldwide Hydrogen Super Highways, 2011 February 23-24 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Series V: Governor's Opportunity Fund files, 2008-2013., Extent: 2.8 cu. ft. (8 boxes) (Box 42-49)
  Series V: Governor's Opportunity Fund files is housed in three boxes and is arranged alphabetically by folder title. This series contains general correspondence, proposals and approved Governor's Opportunity Fund listings and files, pertaining to economic development during the Governor Robert McDonnell's Administration. The files usually contain fund requests from the Virginia Economic Development Partnership and/or memorandums from Secretary Cheng to Governor McDonnell requesting approval of grants.
  The Governor's Opportunity Fund is a pool of discretionary funds available to the Governor to secure a business location or expansion project in Virginia. Grants are awarded to localities on a local matching basis with the expectation that the grant will result in a favorable location decision for the Commonwealth. The Virginia Investment Partnership is a discretionary performance incentive to encourage continued capital investment by Virginia companies.
  - Abbott Nutrition, 2010 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - AAFFG (Silly Putty), 2011 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - ACE Hardware, 2011 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - ACME, 2013 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - AES, 2010 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Airbus, 2012-2013 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Albany Industries, 2011 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Alenia T-100, 2010 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Alexander Industries, 2013 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Altria, 2010 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Amazon.com, 2011-2012 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - American Alliance Financial and Funding Group, 2010 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - American Axle, 2012 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Amsted Rail, 2012 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Applied High Performance Computing, 2010 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Ardagh Metal Packaging, 2013 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Areva, 2012-2013 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Ashland, Inc., 2010-2011 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Ashley Furniture, 2011 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges, 2010 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - American of Martinsville, 2010 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Atlantic Sapphire, 2012 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Atomized Products, 2013 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Aubert & Duval S.A. (Obelix), 2010-2011 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - AVIS, 2010 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Axxor, USA, Inc., 2011 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - AYNA (Alone Yet Not Alone Film), 2011 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Backcountry.com, 2011 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Babcock & Wilcox Co., 2010 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Balchem Corp., 2012 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - BASF North America, 2012 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Bassett Corp., 2013 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Bayshore Concrete, 2013 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - BaySys International, 2010 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Bechtel Corp., 2011 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Becton Dickenson, 2010 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Berryville Graphics, 2012 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Big R Bridge, 2012 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Boeing, 2010 (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Booz Allen Hamilton, 2010 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Bristol Compressors Int., 2011 (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - Browning Transport Management, 2013 (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Cadence, Inc., 2011 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Cadillac Casting, Inc., 2010 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Canon, 2010-2013 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Capital One, 2010-2012 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Carded Graphics, LLC, 2012 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Carmel Church Station, 2008-2010 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Carmeuse Lime and Stone, 2012 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Celanese Acetate, LLC, 2012 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Center Point, 2010 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - CFA Institute, 2011 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Chesapeake Cartridge Corporation, 2012 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Choice Hotels, 2010 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Cicame Energie, Inc., 2010 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Cobia Farms, 2010 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Colgate-Palmolive, 2013 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Colt Manufacturing, 2011 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Commonwealth Laminating & Coating, Inc., 2011-2012 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Continental Chassis & Safety, 2011 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Continental Waste Managment, LLC, 2011 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Corporate Executive Beard Company, 2013 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Corsi Cabinet Co., 2012-2013 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Corning Incorp., 2012 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Cosentino USA, 2012 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - CTL Packaging, 2011 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - CTMS, Inc., 2010 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Cvent, Inc., 2013 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Dassault, 2012 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - DBD Biofuels, Inc., 2013 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Delta Star, Inc., 2010-2011 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Daikin McQuay, 2012-2013 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Digital Data Divide (Project America), 2013 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Dominion Packaging, Inc., 2013 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - DRS Technologies, 2012 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  - DuPont Energy Storage, 2010 (Box 43, Folder 34)
  - Dynax, 2011 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  - Eastman Performance Films (Project West), 2013 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - eBay, Inc., 2012 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - ecoFuels, LLC, 2012-2013 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Electrovaya (Electro), 2010 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Elmet Technologies, Inc., 2010 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - El Rosal, 2013 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Emergent BioSolutions, 2012 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Encell Technology, LLC, 2010-2011 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Engility, 2012 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Enviva LP, 2011 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Evatron, LLC, 2010 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Evolution Resources, 2010 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Evonik Goldschmidt, 2013 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Euro-Composites Corp., 2010 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Falls Stamping, 2013 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Fanevil, 2011 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - FASTC (Foreign Affairs Security Training Center), 2010 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Federal Mogul, Corp., 2012-2013 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Federal projects, 2010 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Ferraro Foods, 2011 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Fever Powertrain, 2012-2013 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Flowers Food, 2010 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Food Lion, 2010 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Freight Car America, Inc., 2010 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Fulchum Concepts, LLC, 2011-2012 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Gates Coporation, 2011 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - General Dynamics, 2010 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - GE Aviation, 2011-2012 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Genesis Products, Incorp., 2011 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - GeoEye, 2010 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Genworth Financial, Inc., 2011 (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Gilco International Lumber, 2012 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - GKN, 2012 (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Global Safety Textiles, LLC, 2011 (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Go Daddy Group, Inc., 2010 (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - Goodyear, 2010 (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Green Distribution, 2013 (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - Green Mountain Coffee Roasters, Inc., 2011 (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - Hampton Farms/Severn Peanut Co., 2013 (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - Hanwha Azdel, Inc., 2013 (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - Hardide Coatings, 2013 (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - HDT Engineered Technologies, 2010 (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - Hershey, 2010 (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - High Liner Foods, 2012-2013 (Box 44, Folder 44)
  - Hilton, 2012-2013 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Holladay Properties, ca. 2010 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Hollister, 2013 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Home Care Industries, 2010 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Honeywell, Inc., 2011-2012 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - HP Hood, LLC, 2013 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Hornschuch, 2010 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Huntington Ingalls, Incorp., 2012 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Ibiden Co., Ltd., 2010 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - ICF International, 2010-2011 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - idX Impressions, 2013 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Iluka Resources, 2012-2013 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - IMS Gear, 2011 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - InBev, 2010 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Intelsat Corp., 2012 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - International Paper, 2010-2011 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - ITT Defense, 2011 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - James Hardie, 2013 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Jimmy Ash, LLC, 2012 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - K2M Corp., 2013 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Kalahari Project, 2010 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - KDH Defense Systems, Inc., 2011 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Kilgour Industries, 2013 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Klausner Group, 2010-2011 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Project Sun Day (Korean Solar Project), 2010 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Korona Candles, Inc., 2013 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - KPMG, 2010 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Kraft Foods, 2010-2012 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - K-VA-T, 2011 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Kyma Technologies, 2011 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Laminate Technologies, Inc., 2011-2012 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - Laird & Company, 2010 (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - Lhoist North America, 2013 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Liaoyang Ningfeng Woodenware Co., 2013 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - Liebherr, 2012 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - Lincoln (movie), 2010-2011 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Lipton Tea, 2012 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Living Social, 2012 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Lockheed Martin, 2010-2012 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Loudoun Baseball, 2009-2010 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Mack with Cheese (movie), 2010 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Mars, Inc., 2010-2011 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Martinsville Speedway, 2010 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - McKee Foods, 2012 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - McKeeson Corp., 2012 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - McKinley-Ross, 2012 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - McQuay, 2011 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Mead Westvaco, 2010-2011 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Mercury Paper, 2010-2011 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - MiaSole, 2011 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Micron Technology, 2010-2013 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Microsoft, 2010-2012 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - MicroAire Surgical Instruments, LLC, 2010-2011 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Mitsubishi, 2010-2013 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Monogram Food Solutions, 2010 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Montebello Packaging, 2010-2011 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Morgan Lumber Company, Inc., 2010 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Morningstar Foods (White Wave Foods), 2012 (Box 46, Folder 232)
  - National Academy of Environmental Design, 2011 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Navy Federal Credit Union, 2012 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - New Belgium Brewing Co., 2011-2012 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - New Dawn (Project New Dawn), 2012 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Northrop Grumman, 2010-2013 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Noblis, 2011 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - North American Mold Technology, LLC, 2013 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Nosco, 2013 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Oceaneering International, Inc., 2013 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Project Odyssey, 2010 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Olympus Dairy, 2012 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Omega Protein, Inc., 2011 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Orion Air Group, 2010 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - O'Sullivan Films Company, 2010 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - PEOPLExpress (Project Freedom), 2012 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Pepco Holdings, ca. 2010 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Performance Friction Corp., 2012 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - PepsiCo., 2013 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Pfizer-Fareva, S.A., 2010-2011 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Phoenix Packaging Operations, LLC, 2010-2012 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Polymer Group, Inc., 2010 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Porter's Fabrications, 2013 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - PPD, Inc., 2010 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Proactive, 2011 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Project CSS, 2012-2013 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Project Cutting Edge, 2013 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Project Sun, 2013 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Project X-Cel, 2012 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Pruefrex, 2012 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Raytheon, 2010-2013 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - R.B. Mining, 2013 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Redskins (Washington Football), 2012-2013 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Renmatrix, 2011-2012 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Robinson Solutions, 2011 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - RockTenn Co., 2011 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Rolls Royce, 2009 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - RTI International Meals, Inc., 2011 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Rubbermaid Commercial Products, 2011 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Sabra Dipping Co., 2011-2013 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Safety Technologies, Incorp., 2011 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Science Applications International, Corp., 2010 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Schletter Incorp., 2011-2012 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Scholle Packaging, 2012 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Siemens Energy, Inc., 2012 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Sears, 2011 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Shamrock Foods, 2012-2013 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Shearer's Foods, 2013 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Sheetz, 2012 (Box 48, Folder 9a)
  - Shop-Vac Corp., 2011 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Sierra Nevada Brewing Co., 2011 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Sigmatex, 2013 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Smurfit-Stone, 2010-2011 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Social & Scientific Systems, 2012 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Sodexo North America, 2012 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Southern Finishing Co., 2010 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Sports Quest, 2010 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Sprint, 2011 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Steel Fab Company, 2013 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Sterlite Optical Technologies, Ltd., 2012 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Sun Coke Energy, Inc., 2013 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Sun Day, 2011 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Sunny Z Foods, 2013 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Superior Dairy, 2010 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Swordfish, 2012 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Syria Innovations, 2010-2012 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Tak Investments, 2011-2012 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Taurus 80, 2013 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - TE Connectivity, 2013 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Tecro-Taiwan, 2010 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - TeleTech Holdings, 2012 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - Tempur-Pedic, 2012 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - Tessy Plastics Corp., 2011 (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - Toray Carbon Fibers America, 2012-2013 (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - Touring Development Financing Program (East Village), 2012 (Box 48, Folder 35)
  - Tread Corp., 2011 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Trinity Packaging Corp., 2009-2013 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Turn (Series), 2013 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Tyson Foods, Inc., 2011 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Unilewer Manufacturing, Inc., 2013 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Universal Custom Millwork, Inc., 2010-2011 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - VCI (Virginia Casting Industries), LLC, 2010 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - VeriSign, 2010 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - VFP, Inc., 2013 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Visa, Inc., 2013 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Vitamin Shoppe, 2012 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Volkswagen, 2010 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Volvo, 2011 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - VOW (Virginia Offshore Wind) Coalition, ca. 2010 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Western Refinery, 2010-2011 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Wheeling Corrugating, 2010 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Whitewave Foods Co., 2013 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Williamsburg Pottery, ca. 2010 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Wood Fuel Developers, 2010-2011 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Woodgrain Millwork, 2012 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Misc., 2010-2011 (Box 49, Folder 21)